Guide to the Leonard S. Marcus Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- August 2016 Acquisition, circa 1988-2015; 3.67; (4 boxes)
  - Other Short Works and Events, 1988-2015; 1.5; (2 boxes)
    - Where the Wild Books Are, New School, 2015-04-18 (Box 100, Folder 2457)
    - Frances Foster memorial, 2014-09-17 (Box 100, Folder 2458)
    - Publishers Weekly articles about China, 2014-09-11 (Box 101, Folder 2459)
    - Eric Carle Museum Lewis Carroll program, 2015-11-22 (Box 101, Folder 2460)
    - Hagerstown, Maryland, 2015-11-08 (Box 101, Folder 2461)
    - Bank Street Book Fest, 2015-10-24 (Box 101, Folder 2462)
    - Charlotte Zolotow program, 2014-06 (Box 101, Folder 2463)
    - Arne Nixon Center, 2013-03-19 (Box 101, Folder 2464)
    - Grolier Club, 2015-01-20 (Box 101, Folder 2465)
    - Richard Lewis, undated (Box 101, Folder 2466)
    - Touchstone Center, 2014-09-27 (Box 101, Folder 2467)
    - St. John the Divine, 2012-11-29 (Box 101, Folder 2468)
    - Irving Arts Center, 2015-06-13 (Box 101, Folder 2469)
    - Bank Street, Kwame Alexander and Dr. Curtis Alexander, 2015-04-06 (Box 101, Folder 2470)
    - University of Pennsylvania symposium "Creating Children's Books", 2014-10-17 (Box 101, Folder 2471)
    - Global Kids Connect, 2015-12-02 (Box 101, Folder 2472)